"Qiu Yuan's Old Words"
「邱源の古い言葉」
Qiu Yuan's old words, hello, everyone
邱源の昔の言葉、皆さん、こんにちは。
The guards of our hospital commemorate the 130th birthday of Mr. Hu Shi, President Gu
当院の警備員が古国家主席胡施氏の生誕130周年を祝う
Specially hold a feast of knowledge this month
今月は特別に知識の饗宴を開催します
The speakers invited by President Hu Shi for the popular science lectures are
胡施国家主席が人気科学講演会に招待した講演者は以下の通り。
Winner of Hu Shi Memorial Research Lecture in 1909
1909年胡施記念研究講演会受賞者
Qiu Zhonglin, a researcher at the Institute of History of our school
本校歴史研究所研究員邱忠林
Lecture for us on the history of hoarding and cutting money in Chinese history
中国の歴史におけるお金の貯め込みと切り捨ての歴史についての講義
Researcher Qiu Zhonglin was a postdoctoral fellow at the Institute of History, National Taiwan University in 1997
研究者 Qiu Zhonglin は、1997 年に国立台湾大学歴史研究所の博士研究員でした。
Said a teacher in the History Department of Danjiang University
丹江大学史学科の教師はこう語った。
Since 2001, he has been working as a research officer in 11 institutes of our hospital
2001年より当院の11の研究所で研究員として勤務。
work so far
これまでの仕事
He was awarded the 2006
他成獲2006年本院
Research Writing Award for Young Scholars
若手研究者のためのリサーチライティング賞
Ministry of Science and Technology 2018
科技部2018年度
Outstanding Research Award
優秀研究賞
And last year with a festival ceremony to mobilize
そして昨年はフェスティバルのセレモニーを動員して
A research project centered on the official village camp activities of the Youth League
青年団公式村キャンプ活動を中心とした研究プロジェクト
Won the Hu Shih Memorial Research Award
胡適記念研究賞を受賞
Researcher Qiu has long been committed to the social and cultural history of the Minqing Youth League
研究者邱氏は、長年にわたって民清の社会文化史に取り組んできました。
and Material Culture Studies
および物質文化研究
Talking about the topic
主題多言
Includes blue material drainage medical system
青色の素材のドレナージ医療システムが含まれています
spending history
支出履歴
in Chinese history
中国の歴史の中で
Good at separating records, etc.
レコードなどの分別が得意。
In the near future, it focuses on the military epidemic prevention system of the Ming Dynasty
近未来、明代の軍事防疫システムに焦点を当てる
and long-distance travel history
そして長距離の旅行歴
Today he will share with us
今日、彼は私たちと分かち合います
The record of collective segregation in the history of China
中国の歴史における集団隔離の記録
And examine the cultural explanations of the ancients for this phenomenon
そして、この現象についての古代人の文化的説明を調べてください。
Listen carefully to the wonderful and promising background content
素晴らしく有望な背景コンテンツを注意深く聞いてください
Welcome to Researcher Qiu Zhonglin
研究員 Qiu Zhonglin へようこそ
Dean of Defense, Hello, audience.
国防部長、こんにちは、聴衆の皆さん。
It is a great honor to be invited by the academy to give a lecture today
本日はアカデミーから講演に招待していただき大変光栄です
The topic I'm going to talk about has been reported by the chief of defense.
私が話そうとしているテーマは国防長官から報告されたものです。
I'll just start talking
ちょっと話し始めます
Research on this topic actually collected materials very early
このテーマに関する研究は実際に非常に早い段階で資料を収集しました
generally speaking
一般的に言えば
There are very scattered records about money cutting in Jintun in Chinese history
中国の歴史の中で、金屯での金切りに関する記録は非常に散在しています。
Distributed in history books, local characters and some notes
歴史書やご当地キャラクター、メモなどに掲載
The time span is relatively long, starting from the Han Dynasty
時代は比較的長く、漢の時代から始まります。
until contemporary
現代まで
presumably can be disconnected probably in 1949
おそらく1949年には切断できると思われる
Because this after 1949
1949年以降だから
Many newspapers and periodicals are actually in mainland China
多くの新聞や定期刊行物は実際に中国本土にあります
i can't collect
集められない
So basically I probably won't discuss
基本的には議論しないと思います
There are records about this
これに関する記録が残っている
let's start now
今すぐ始めましょう
purpose of this study
この研究の目的
mainly through data analysis
主にデータ分析を通じて
The natural history of fine hoarding
ファイン・ホーディングの自然史
With this space-time background stranded with it
立ち往生したこの時空背景で
The reason for the shallow cut and the cultural explanation
浅いカットの理由と文化的説明
is also the part I'm going to discuss
これもこれからお話しする部分です
But it's a pity
でも残念だ
Written Records of Chinese Social Pollutants and Governance
中国の社会汚染物質と統治に関する書面による記録
Relatively probably a little more than the West and Japan
比較的、おそらく西洋や日本より少し多い
But there is very little image data
ただし画像データが少ない
And even with this profile of this image
そして、この画像のこのプロフィールでも
It draws this fine and shallow look
この繊細で浅い表情を描きます
also very ridiculous
それもとてもばかばかしい
You can read from that poster
そのポスターから読み取れます
can be seen
見られます
The one on the seal is basically from the late Qing Dynasty
印章にあるものは基本的に清朝末期のものです。
"Time is in the pictorial"
「時間は絵の中にある」
A picture drawn of Jintun Shallow
金屯浅を描いた絵
But he drew the goldfish to look like a carp
でも彼は金魚を鯉のように描いた
It also represents our traditional literati
それは私たちの伝統的な文人を代表するものでもあります
I'm drawing this about the sea
海について描いています
Huge catch-like animals when
巨大な獲物のような動物のとき
their understanding
彼らの理解
He and these fishes inland
彼とこの魚たちは内陸にいる
almost the same
ほぼ同じ
From this perspective
この観点から見ると
In fact, far behind
実はずっと後ろに
Japan and the West
日本と西洋
We'll see a picture later
後で写真を見てみましょう
That's a picture of the West
それは西洋の写真です
in Chinese history
中国の歴史の中で
Crunchy Jintun shallow record
ザクザクジントゥンシャローレコード
probably belong to the two sides
おそらく両方の側に属します
in 16 BC
紀元前16年
In the place Beihaijun in Shandong
山東省北海君という場所で
Once there was a big fish shallow
かつて、浅瀬に大きな魚がいた
on this coast
この海岸で
Six long and one tall, there are four in total
長さが6本、高さが1本、合計4本あります
Then in 4 BC, probably in Donglai County, Shandong
その後紀元前 4 年、おそらく山東省東来県で
There is also Lantau cutting money in Pingdu
平度には大嶼島の金切りもある
There are seven in total, all dead.
合計7名で全員死亡。
In AD 173 also in Donglai County
西暦173年には東来県でも
The sea pushed two more Lantaus onto the coast
海はさらに2頭のランタウスを海岸に押し上げた
Its length is eight or nine sheets, and its height is about one sheet.
長さは8～9枚、高さは1枚程度です。
The terms used by the two sides of the Taiwan Strait to cut money from Jinyintun
台湾海峡の両側が金銀屯からの資金を削減するために使用した用語
In fact, until now, especially in the Ming and Qing Dynasties
実際、これまで、特に明と清の時代には
Even in modern times, some people are saying that this phenomenon is called sea pig Lantau
現代でもこの現象を海豚ランタオ島と呼ぶ人もいる
It refers to gold and copper cutting money
金や銅がお金を切ることを指します
I just said that this is a plate of Henan in the West
これは西部の河南省の皿だと言いました
We drew this goldfish cutting pliers
この金魚ペンチを描きました
That's a pair of incense-smeared gold cutting pliers
それはお香のついた金ペンチです
it's very realistic
とても現実的です
Even its genitals are drawn
性器まで描かれている
And it can be seen from the ratio of it to people.
そして、それは人々との比率からもわかります。
But we in China are very short of such image materials
しかし、中国ではそのような画像素材が非常に不足しています。
And the director of the painting is very wrong
そしてこの絵の監督は非常に間違っています
it's a pity
それは残念だ
On the Japanese side, in fact, because of their tradition
実際、日本ではその伝統により、
The supplementary gold industry is very developed
補助的な金産業は非常に発展しています
So they were in the 17th and 18th centuries
つまり、彼らは17世紀と18世紀にいたのです
There are also many pictures of this kind of supplementary money left behind.
このような補助金の写真もたくさん残されています。
Images of various types of gold painted inside
内側に様々な種類の金を描いたイメージ
are also very accurate
も非常に正確です
China may have entered the sea in the long-term Ming and Qing Dynasties
中国は明と清の長期にわたる海洋進出を果たした可能性がある
And the message to the ocean is not that big
そして海へのメッセージはそれほど大きくない
Therefore, the first image data left is very little
そのため、最初に残っている画像データはごくわずかです
The second factory manager is not accurate
2番目の工場長は正確ではありません
we're going to take a look now
今から見てみます
There are some records about Jintun’s offshore activities in Chinese history
中国の歴史には金屯の海洋活動に関する記録がいくつかある。
give some examples
いくつか例を挙げてください
First of all, in Hebei near Shangguan Customs
まずは河北省上関税関付近
on the coast of this place
この場所の海岸で
it is documented
それは文書化されています
There will be a very large fish in this place
この場所にはとても大きな魚がいるでしょう
This is called bigger than a square
これを正方形より大きいといいます
called yellow croaker
イエローニベと呼ばれる
sometimes it cuts shallow on the shore
時には岸が浅くなることもあります
After the locals cut the meat
地元の人たちが肉を切った後
take it to boil oil
油を沸騰させるために持って行きます
This record lasted from the Ming Dynasty to the Qing Dynasty
この記録は明の時代から清の時代まで続いた
There are relevant records
関連する記録があります
until the Republic of China
中華民国まで
Here in Bohai Bay
ここ渤海湾
Fishermen of this generation in the Bohai Sea
渤海のこの世代の漁師たち
still call the gold class the old yellow croaker
今でもゴールドクラスをオールドキニチと呼んでいます
But the name of Jintun in various places
しかし、さまざまな場所で金屯の名前が
It's not the same
同じではない
Hebei called yellow croaker
河北省の黄ニベと呼ばれる
But this Shandong coast
しかし、この山東海岸は
also known as squid
別名ナマズ
For example, it is said in a record at the place of the yellow line in the last year of the dynasty that
例えば、王朝末年の黄線の場所の記録にはこう記されている。
He said that this fish is often ten or twenty feet long
彼は、この魚は体長が10フィートか20フィートであることが多いと言いました
Every time they are active on the sea, they are in groups of three or four
彼らは海上で活動するときは常に3～4頭の群れで行動します。
and spray that wave
そしてその波をスプレーします
It looks like it's snowing
雪が降っているようです
Anyway, his record is quite realistic.
とにかく、彼の記録は非常に現実的です。
It's because Jintun has a habit
ジントゥンには癖があるからだ
It will spray air upwards in front of the air hole
空気穴の前から上向きに空気を噴射します
The jet will cause a shower of snow that looks like
ジェットは次のような雪のシャワーを引き起こします。
In it, he also specifically recorded that this kind of Jintun
その中で、彼はまた、この種の金屯についても具体的に記録しました
He can even swallow a boat when his mouth opens
口が開くとボートを飲み込むことさえできる
So sometimes it's called swallowing a boat
だから時々それはボートを飲み込むと呼ばれる
There are relevant records until the Republic of China
中華民国まで関連記録が残っている
There is a man in Wei County, Shandong, who is a scholar named Chen Hengqing
山東省渭県に陳恒清という学者がいる。
He mentioned in it that the place near the sea is often
彼は海の近くの場所がよくあると言いました
There will be dragon soldiers on the sea
海には竜兵がいるだろう
Jintun
金屯
Dragon soldiers
竜兵
Dragon soldiers pass by
竜兵が通り過ぎる
The leader of the gunfish
ガンフィッシュのリーダー
There will be holes in the top of the fish
魚の上部に穴が開いてしまいます
it jets
それは噴射します
The breath comes out and there is sound with sound
息が出て音が出る
looks like a cannon
大砲のように見える
This is the record in Shandong
これは山東省での記録です
Now let's see that this is
これが次のことであることを見てみましょう
the way it blows
吹き方
But in Jiangsu this place is called
しかし、江蘇省ではこの場所はこう呼ばれています
There is nothing special about Jintun class
ジントゥンには特別なことは何もありません
some titles
いくつかのタイトル
But it is most often referred to as
しかし、最もよく言われるのは、
a very large fish usually called a quarter fish
通常クォーターフィッシュと呼ばれる非常に大きな魚
Sometimes it's funny when you read this record
この記録を読むと時々面白いことがあります
Just think it looks like a carp
鯉に似ていると思ってください
and it will be in
そしてそれは入ります
This one on the sea is tumbling in the air
海上のこれが空中を転がっている
This is of course a very realistic record.
もちろん、これは非常に現実的な記録です。
This place in Fujian is quite special.
福建省のこの場所は非常に特別です。
that is
あれは
For example, in Fujian, let’s look at the Matsu
たとえば、福建省の馬祖を見てみましょう。
This place in Lianjiang County
連江県のこの場所
It is recorded that they often have
彼らはしばしば持っていたと記録されています
Four species of this fish related to Jintun
金屯に関連するこの魚の 4 種
what's their name
彼らの名前は何ですか
But the first one he called the porcupine fish
しかし彼が最初に呼んだ魚はハリセンボンだった
He said that the nose will spray air
彼は鼻から空気を噴霧するだろうと言いました
In addition, CNOOC
さらに、CNOOC
That's the biggest possibility
それが最大の可能性だ
Refers to this relatively large type of gold
この比較的大きな種類の金を指します
Another third type is called sea pigs
別の 3 番目のタイプはシーピッグと呼ばれます
But if you use this local dialect
でもこの地方の方言を使うと
How about comparing this sea pig with a sea pig?
この海豚と海豚を比べてみてはいかがでしょうか？
Put it all together, it might actually be the same fish
全部並べてみると、実は同じ魚かもしれない
That's the dolphin
あれはイルカです
It's actually the same as that A and that sea pig.
実はあのAと海豚と同じなんです。
But he recorded that it is divided into two types
しかし、彼はそれが2つのタイプに分けられると記録しました
In addition, he also recorded a fourth species called cross fish
さらに、クロスフィッシュと呼ばれる 4 番目の種も記録しました。
That
それか
In this cross fish, it is also specifically written that
このクロスフィッシュには具体的にこうも書かれています。
it belongs to shark
それはサメのものです
but you get used to it
でも慣れますよ
That is to say, we have the habit of looking at the records behind it.
つまり、私たちはその背後にある記録を見る習慣があるのです。
you know it's probably tiger spirit or something
おそらくタイガースピリットか何かだと思います
It's closer to that
それはそれに近いです
Shark-like teeth are sharp
サメのような歯は鋭い
And it's the biting kind
そしてそれは噛むタイプです
that's how it rolls
それが転がる方法です
Because if a shark doesn't have this habit
サメにこの習性がなかったら
In short, basically in this place in Fujian
つまり、基本的には福建省のこの場所で
The records of fine buttocks are relatively detailed
細かいお尻の記録は比較的詳細です
Of course, the classification above in traditional records is sometimes compared
もちろん、伝統的な記録における上記の分類が比較されることもあります。
Not so different from our modern natural history classification
現代の自然史分類とそれほど変わらない
At that time it was more traditional
当時はもっと伝統的だった
So it's not very precise, it's actually inevitable
つまり、それはあまり正確ではなく、実際には避けられないものです
Then this is what I just mentioned, it is more like the sand
それから、これは私が今言ったものです、それは砂に似ています
floating gold
フローティングゴールド
his appearance
彼の外見
because of the most important feature behind him
彼の背後にある最も重要な特徴のため
Just like a shark, his fins
まるでサメのようなヒレ
he will show the tail fin
彼は尾ひれを見せるだろう
and he looks like a shark
そして彼はサメのように見えます
Now let's look at Taiwan
さて台湾を見てみよう
is Taiwan
台湾です
he continued this
彼はこう続けた
There are some names that are actually a bit like Southern Fujian
実は福建省南部に似た名前がいくつかあります
He speaks in our Taiwanese Hokkien dialect
彼は台湾の福建語の方言で話します
just hi ang
こんにちは
Like this pig spiral in Kangxi
康熙の豚のスパイラルのように
The record is Hayon
記録はハヨン
He is Haiyou
彼はハイヨウです
can swallow a boat
ボートを飲み込むことができる
on the lake water
湖の水の上で
this color on that back
あの背中のこの色
It's like a bull's back
まるで雄牛の背中のようだ
The latter record is the most interesting
後者の記録が最も興味深い
That is to say, as long as he appears
つまり、彼が現れる限り、
the big one will appear
大きいのが現れるだろう
Maybe there's a typhoon or something like that
もしかしたら台風か何かが来るかも知れません
this storm comes out
この嵐が出てくる
in 1722
1722年
In fact, there was an official in the Qing Dynasty who was ordered
実際、清朝に命じられた役人がいました。
Come to Taiwan form
台湾に来てフォーム
it's in it's this
それはこれです
inside this record of the form
このフォームのレコード内で
jellyfish
クラゲ
he said probably
彼はおそらく言った
This local fisherman told him
この地元の漁師は彼に言いました。
About three or four thousand catties
3,000斤くらいか4,000斤くらい
The small one weighs about a thousand kilograms
小さいものでも重さは1000キロくらいある
that sometimes called
時々そう呼ばれます
another name
別の名前
for example
例えば
Later he mentioned this, this sea
後で彼はこの海について言いました
sea ​​tree
海の木
In fact, in Taiwanese, it is Haidu.
実は台湾語では「海都（ハイドゥ）」です。
That is the head looks like a pig
それは頭が豚に似ているということです
The big one weighs about a thousand catties
大きいものは重さ約1000斤あります
The small one is about five or six hundred catties
小さいものは500斤か600斤くらいです
That likes to get up on the water
それは水の上に上がるのが好きです
Then this is very similar to the habit of that dolphin
そうすると、これはあのイルカの習性とよく似ているんです
This is the record of Taiwan
これは台湾の記録です
Actually quite a lot
実はかなり多い
Just moments
ほんの一瞬だけ
let's see now
今見てみましょう
This coast of Guangdong
広東省のこの海岸
Its record actually has some
その記録には実際にいくつかの記録があります
With Minnan and the one just mentioned
ミンナンと先ほどの人と
The record in the northern part of the lake is almost the same
湖北部の記録もほぼ同じ
You see, the first type is sea pigs
ほら、最初のタイプは海豚です
that ball is the second category
そのボールは2番目のカテゴリーです
The third category is called Baifeng
3番目のカテゴリは百峰と呼ばれます
thanks to the wind
風のおかげで
it means big
それは大きいという意味です
Much like this sea pig but he likes to jump
この海豚によく似ていますが、彼はジャンプするのが好きです
But I think this one might be related to Class A.
しかし、これはおそらくクラスAに関連していると思います。
In fact, it was when he was observing
実際、それは彼が観察していたときでした
What you see is his different shape
あなたが見ているのは彼の異なる姿です
In addition, there is a record in the political years
さらに政治時代にも記録が残っている
This is of course closer to the South China Sea.
もちろん、ここは南シナ海に近いです。
This, that, Zhao Qingfu, this place
あれ、あれ、趙清福、この場所
It's in the Yangjiang area
陽江地区にあります
He has three types of gold
彼は3種類のゴールドを持っています
The first type is called sea loach
最初のタイプはドジョウと呼ばれます
The second type is called cattle fish
2番目のタイプはキャトルフィッシュと呼ばれます
third call
3回目の電話
Then in terms of his category
それでは彼のカテゴリーに関して言えば、
basically already relatively possible
基本的にはすでに比較的可能です
slightly better
わずかに良くなった
That is to say
つまり
tradition for that
そのための伝統
Especially after the Ming and Qing dynasties
特に明と清の時代以降
As for the activities of that goldfish on the surface of the sea
あの金魚の海面での活躍は
And his classification has begun to be more detailed
そして彼の分類はより詳細になり始めました
Before the Ming Dynasty, there were relatively few
明の時代以前は比較的少なかった
There was just a document mentioned above
ちょうど上記のような文書がありました
It's his goldfish on the back of his fish
彼の魚の背中にいるのは彼の金魚です
sometimes some
時々いくつかの
parasitic things
寄生的東西
That's actually Fujitora
それはまさに藤虎です
Fujitora will parasitize in
藤虎が寄生します
Especially this sad one with some whales
特にクジラがいるこの悲しいもの
there are some records
いくつかの記録があります
it's not just on the sea
それは海の上だけではありません
And it has already swam into the inner river and the inner border
そしてそれはすでに内なる川と内なる国境へと泳ぎ込んでしまった
There are many records
たくさんの記録があります
The earliest record is in AD 837
最古の記録は西暦 837 年にあります
There is a big fishing ground slipping up
大きな漁場がずり落ちている
Swim from that Yellow Sea into this Huaihe River
あの黄海から泳いでこの淮河へ
later on that
それについては後で
Many people in this place killed him
この場所にいた多くの人が彼を殺した
That was until the early years of the Republic of China
それは中華民国の初期まででした
In this Haizhou area is the Lianjiang
この海州エリアには連江があります。
The one near Lianyungang
連雲港の近く
because there are some
いくつかあるので
there are some rivers
いくつかの川があります
It was dug by hand
手で掘ったものです
This kind of river connected with the canal
運河とつながっているこんな川
There will often be some Jintun Lie swimming in
ジントゥン・リーが泳いでいることがよくあります。
One of them is Guanhe
そのうちの1人はGuanheです
But every July and August
でも毎年7月と8月には
There is that Uyghur gold
ウイグルの黄金があります
He swam inward from that estuary
彼は川の河口から内側に向​​かって泳いだ
but he is weird
でも彼は変だ
He swam to one place and went back
彼はある場所まで泳いで戻っていきました
That place is in the Dragon King Temple
その場所は龍王神殿の中にあります
So the local folks said that it was a goldfish to worship the Dragon King
そこで地元の人々は、龍神を祀るための金魚だと言いました。
I'll go back after saying goodbye
別れを告げたらまた行きます
The Yangtze River is very special
長江はとても特別な場所です
Everyone knows him because of the Yangtze River
長江の名前で誰もが彼を知っています
The Yangtze River is very wide
長江はとても広いです
The collar is also very large
襟も大きめです
So this goldfish he swam in
それで彼が泳いだこの金魚は
sometimes very big
時々とても大きい
For example, in the Southern Tang Dynasty
たとえば、南唐の時代には
During the Five Dynasties, when the descendants of the Southern Tang Dynasty
五代時代、南唐の子孫
There is a big sea ball
大きなシーボールがあります
he started from
彼はから始めました
He described it as a big body
彼はそれを大きな体だと表現した
cut money there
そこで金を切る
It says that the long tree is a funeral
長い木はお葬式だそうです
Near the current Jiujiang
現在の九江付近
That's the place in Jiujiang, Hukou of Boyang Lake, where the money is cut.
それが博洋湖の湖口九江にある金を切る場所だ。
Then why can we judge that he is Jintun class?
では、なぜ彼が金屯級であると判断できるのでしょうか？
Because he was still spraying water when he was on fire
火事が起きてもまだ水を噴霧していたからだ
It's the water, it's the air
それは水です、それは空気です
Spray paint from the brain
脳からスプレーペイント
The following is the one about Dongting Lake
以下は洞庭湖についてです。
It is recorded in the young magenta clay potion of Dongting Lake that
洞庭湖の若い赤紫色の粘土薬には次のように記録されています。
This fisherman in the area of ​​Dongting Lake
洞庭湖の漁師さん
will catch this jerk
この野郎を捕まえるだろう
This is Jiang hip
これがジャンヒップです
It may be a different experience than the one swimming in above.
上で泳ぐのとはまた違った体験ができるかもしれません。
Use various schemes to catch
さまざまなスキームを使って捕まえる
looks a little cruel
少し残酷に見える
In fact, the record of the buttocks of the Yangtze River is very early.
実際、長江のお尻の記録は非常に古いものです。
Someone once verified that
かつて誰かがそれを検証した
There is a word in goose and duck called remember
ガチョウとアヒルには「覚えておく」という言葉があります
This should be that white butt
これがあの白いお尻のはずだ
that of course might be a bit far fetched
もちろんそれは少し突飛かもしれません
However, we can see from the records in the literature that
しかし、文献の記録からわかることは、
That is, at least in the Ming Dynasty
つまり、少なくとも明の時代には
like in 1564
1564年のような
In fact, in this Jiangnan area
実はこの江南地域では
There is such a record of Bai Jiyu
白吉宇にはこんな記録があります
he is white
彼は白人です
later cut money
後でお金を切ります
Of course this record is very special
もちろんこのレコードはとても特別なものだ
That is to say, at that time, there were many sea areas heading towards this area.
つまり当時はこの海域に向かう海域が多かったということだ。
This Xinyangjiang this
この新陽江はこれ
Jiangai
建外
It's very loud, like a cow is braying
すごくうるさくて、まるで牛が鳴いているみたいだ
More than 1,000 people went to see
1,000人以上の人が見に行きました
But then there are some people who don't know what to do
でも、どうすればいいのか分からない人もいるでしょう
swim into a small river port
小さな川の港に泳いで入る
He was later found alive
彼は後に生きているのが発見された
Just cut money on the river beach
川辺でお金を切るだけ
was finally killed
ついに殺された
This is Baijitun
こちらは白吉屯です
Of course Baijitun on the Yangtze River
もちろん長江の白吉屯も
There is very little stock now
現在在庫が非常に少なくなっております
Become a rare unarmed
レアな非武装になる
have been included in their
彼らの中に含まれています
China's protected animals
中国の保護動物
animal protection
動物保護
In addition, we have to look at
さらに、次の点にも注目する必要があります。
Like some aspects of this record
このレコードのいくつかの側面のように
Also this record is what the front hall said
また、この記録はフロントホールが言ったことです
There are other related records
他にも関連する記録があります
This is another picture of Baijitun
これは白吉屯の別の写真です
In fact, there are related records in Fujian
実際、福建省にも関連する記録が残っています。
We won't talk about the relationship of time
時間の関係については話さない
This place in Jeonju is where we hold
全州のこの場所が私たちが開催する場所です
This example is fine
この例は大丈夫です
It's at the Ma Xiang Hall in Jeonju
全州馬祥ホールです
There was a record in this place that
この場所にこんな記録がありました
It comes from this Tong'an County
この同安県から来ています
A small river in the west is called Xixi
西の小さな川は西渓と呼ばれます
20 miles up
20マイル上空
Now we're talking about that
今、私たちはそれについて話しています
about that Chinese history
その中国の歴史について
This kind of space-time distribution of the money cutting in this gold mine
金屯における金切りのこのような時空分布
I've read about this in total
これについて全部読みました
in the relevant information
関連情報の中で
There are a total of 176 records related to this
これに関連するレコードは合計 176 件あります
among them
その中で
If we divide it according to the four major regions of China
中国の四大地域で分けると
Most of them are in the East China Sea
そのほとんどは東シナ海にあります
A total of 112 times
合計112回
More than the sum of the other three sea areas
他の3海域の合計よりも多い
Why is there more in the East China Sea?
なぜ東シナ海に多いのでしょうか？
maybe the first place is this place
たぶん最初の場所はここです
This colorful shore line is relatively long
このカラフルな海岸線は比較的長いです
The second is that there are two relatively large rivers flowing into the East China Sea.
2つ目は、東シナ海に注ぐ比較的大きな河川が2本あることです。
One is the Yangtze River and the other is the former Yangtze River
1 つは長江、もう 1 つは旧長江です
Their estuaries are very large
彼らの河口は非常に大きいです
near here because there are many lakes with living things and related fish
この近くには生き物やそれに関連する魚が生息する湖がたくさんあるので
So Jintun will hunt here
だからジントゥンはここで狩りをするだろう
may in some cases
場合によっては
He just cut money at the mouth of the Yangtze River and before the mouth of the Yangtze River
彼はちょうど長江の河口と長江の河口の手前でお金を切りました。
This is the classification of the approximate number of times
おおよその回数の分類です
let's take a look
見てみましょう
It's probably the season for him to cut money
おそらく彼にとってはお金を減らす季節だろう
About what months
何月ごろ
First, there is an interesting record
まず、興味深い記録があります
It was in the Jin Dynasty that there was a book called Gu Jinzhu
晋の時代に『顧晋注』という本があった。
he mentioned goldfish
彼は金魚について言及した
Because the ancients regarded this gold as a fish
古代人はこの黄金を魚とみなしたため、
So I held on to them
だから私は彼らにしがみついた
In fact, it should not educate
本来は教育すべきではない
Where is the goldfish hiding in May and June?
5月、6月の金魚はどこに隠れているのでしょうか？
give birth on the shore
海岸で出産する
Then in July and August, it will guide this
その後、7月と8月にこれをガイドします
It's this paper towel and it returns to the sea
このペーパータオルは海に還ります
There will be some walruses on one side and the other will be different
片側にはいくつかのセイウチがあり、もう一方は異なります
Well, there are other records that say
まあ、他にも次のような記録があります
Like the sunny side of this generation in Shandong
山東省のこの世代の晴れた側面のように
Its silkworm season is not in May and June
蚕の季節は5月と6月ではありません
it is march in spring
春の3月です
Then he said that gave birth to this little fish?
それから彼は、それがこの小さな魚を生んだと言いました？
eyes are not open yet
目はまだ開いていません
But it's bigger than three houses
でも家3つ分より大きいよ
That's probably why this place is so miserable
おそらくそれがこの場所がとても悲惨な理由です
Maybe it's a false alarm or something.
もしかしたら誤報か何かかもしれません。
bigger
より大きい
What's more interesting is that
さらに興味深いのは、
In the meaning of Liao disaster
遼災の意味で
Record Shandong Binghai people
山東省の冰海人を記録する
he has a habit
彼には癖がある
That is to say, before and after the Ching Ming Festival
つまり清明節の頃だった。
will see the heavy rain in this sea
この海に大雨が降るだろう
Take his little fish to the sea
彼の小さな魚を海へ連れて行きましょう
go around on land
陸の上を歩き回る
The locals describe it as
地元の人たちはそれを次のように説明します
That is to ask that to bring this son and daughter here
それは、この息子と娘をここに連れてきてほしいということです
That one is called Baimu
あの人はバイムといいます
Of course this is my own imagination
もちろんこれは私の勝手な想像です
human imagination
人間の想像力
Other records are of course different.
他の記録はもちろん異なります。
Maybe the latitude of each sea area
おそらく各海域の緯度
It's different from the temperature of the sea water
海水の温度とは違います
So they are miserable
だから彼らは悲惨なんだよ
It's not the season of misfortune
不幸の季節ではない
Like this area in southwestern Guangdong
広東省南西部のこの地域のように
Records on this sea
この海の記録
That is to say they were in February
つまり2月だったということですね
From this record
この記録から
We don't care how many pages he breeds here
彼がここで何ページ繁殖するかは気にしません
It can be seen that in this coastal place
この海岸沿いの場所でそれがわかります
in the Ming and Qing Dynasties
明と清の時代に
This place, this ocean, this environment are very good
この場所、この海、この環境はとても良いです
So at that time the Jintun class
それで当時のジントゥンクラスは
still very much distributed
まだ非常に多く配布されています
Then I have done statistics on that record
次に、そのレコードについて統計をとりました
This incident in that shallow month
浅い月のこの出来事
Use this record for statistics
このレコードを統計に使用します
Among them, there are about 30 cases in spring.
そのうち、春の件数は約30件あります。
Because there are some documents he only records the year
年しか書かれていない資料もあるから
I won't remember the month and season
月も季節も思い出せない
Some are seasons and some are years
季節を表すものもあれば、年を表すものもあります
So carefully remember the month
だから月を注意深く覚えておいてください
Basically, this figure is relatively speaking
基本的に、この数字は相対的に言えば、
not so much
それほど多くない
But now we can see
しかし今、私たちは見ることができます
That is to say, spring is the most
つまり春が一番
the rest is next in autumn
残りは次は秋です
But the numbers in summer and autumn are not much different.
しかし、夏と秋の数はそれほど変わりません。
Generally speaking, spring 30
一般的に言えば、春30
Most are spring 30
ほとんどが30年春
least winter 21
少なくとも冬21
In fact, there is not much difference in numbers.
実際、数字に大きな違いはありません。
So I can't see if they have a specific
したがって、彼らが特定の機能を持っているかどうかはわかりません
That is to say, in a certain season can
つまり、特定の季節には、
They are easier to cut money
彼らはお金を減らすのが簡単です
so now we're going to look at
それではこれから見ていきます
This is the place where the money was cut
ここがお金を切られた場所です
Let's look at this picture
この写真を見てみましょう
This picture is actually very obvious that it can be seen
この写真は実際に見ると一目瞭然です
It's the place where he cut money
そこは彼が金をカットする場所だ
The first one is in the Bohai Bay
最初のものは渤海湾にあります
It's just what we said
それは私たちが言ったことです
People in Hebei call it Huangyu
河北省の人々はそれを黄玉と呼びます
It's near the Shanghai Customs
上海税関の近くです
On this north side of Bohai Bay
渤海湾のこの北側で
what about this place
この場所はどうですか
There are relatively many records of cutting money
お金を切った実績が比較的多い
The second is Laizhou Bay
2つ目は莱州湾です
from the two men
二人の男から
Laizhou Bay has a lot of records
莱州湾には多くの記録がある
That is to say, we just talked about Beihai County
つまり、北海県について話しました。
Laiju County
来州県
This place is early
この場所は早いです
In the Ming and Qing Dynasties, there were relatively more places in this place
明清時代には、この場所には比較的多くの場所がありました
The third place is Haizhou Bay in the north of Intermodal Port
3位はインターモーダル港の北にある海州湾です
This place borders Shandong and Jiangsu
この場所は山東省と江蘇省に隣接しています
It is also a place with a relatively large curvature.
比較的曲率が大きい場所でもあります。
The vicinity of the intermodal port is because it was the outlet of the Yellow River in the Ming and Qing Dynasties
複合一貫港の近くは、明清の時代に黄河の河口だったことが由来
Because the Yellow River once sucked the Huaihe River
かつて黄河が淮河を吸い込んだため
go to sea from here
ここから海へ行きます
So the area around the intermodal port was also stranded. There are more records.
そのため、複合一貫輸送港の周囲でも立ち往生したという記録が残っています。
The Yangtze Estuary is also a place with many records.
長江河口は多くの記録がある場所でもある。
This is the second most
これは2番目に多いです
Qiantang Bay is the place with the largest number of strandings in the entire record
銭塘湾は全記録の中で最も多くの座礁が発生した場所である
And we now record from the literature that it is the largest number of collective strandings
そして現在、文献から、これが集団座礁の最大数であると記録されています。
also appeared in former don wan
かつてのドンワンにも登場
this place is special
この場所は特別です
is the place to bend the mouth
口を曲げる場所です
The tidal action is sometimes relatively large
潮汐作用が比較的大きくなることがあります
so everyone knows
だからみんな知ってるよ
The Haining tide watcher appeared just to the north of the former guard
海寧の潮監視人が旧警備隊のすぐ北に現れた
when his tide is in a certain season
彼の潮が特定の季節にあるとき
especially during the mid-autumn festival
特に中秋節の時期は
His tide is very high
彼の潮流は非常に高い
This is famous all over the world
これは世界中で有名です
That may be because of the Guanyin of the tide
それは潮の観音のせいかもしれない
Will suck that with some of this fine ass this way
この素晴らしいお尻でそれをしゃぶります
So what about his Ji Zai?
では、彼のジザイはどうなるのでしょうか？
relatively more
比較的多くの
The other number that collectively stranded
集団的に立ち往生したもう一つの番号
we'll give it later
後であげます
next is
次は
wednesday island generation
周三島一代
Because his island is also distributed more
彼の島ももっと分布しているので
And it is the largest fishing ground in China
そして中国最大の漁場です
All kinds of fish are here
あらゆる種類の魚がここにいます
there are a lot of resources
資源はたくさんあります
There are many fish resources
魚類資源非常多
Maybe Jintun is here to supplement the food.
おそらくジントゥンは食料を補充するためにここにいます。
The situation is also more obvious
状況もより明らかです
that sometimes in some
それは時々ある部分では
They ran aground by accident
彼らは偶然座礁した
this is that number
これがその番号です
Everyone can take a look
誰でも見ることができます
There are a total of 45 incidents in Qiantangwan and 35 incidents in the mouth of the Yangtze River. These are the two largest and most
銭塘湾では計45件、長江河口では計35件の事件が発生しており、この2つが最大かつ最多である。
The reason for the song spring, the traditional records about the song spring, why is there a song spring? There are very few records of this
歌泉の理由、歌泉に関する伝統的な記録、なぜ歌泉があるのか​​? この記録は非常に少ないです。
The first record tells that the ocean will have this kind of inertia every autumn.
最初の記録は、海が毎年秋にこの種の慣性を持つことを示しています。
It will start to be called a habit that will push some things on the sea surface to the land
海面にあるものを陸地に押し出す習性と呼ばれるようになる
The local people recorded that these are the three sayings about the people nearby
地元の人々は、これらが近くの人々についての3つのことわざであると記録しました
He said it would push something up
彼はそれが何かを押し上げるだろうと言いました
push push push some damn fish inland
押して押して、いまいまいましい魚を内陸に押し込んでください
Pushing up this phenomenon is called Xihai
この現象を押し上げることを西海といいます。
So in the process some big fish will also
その過程で、いくつかの大きな魚も
just up there
すぐそこにある
The Western missionary at the end of the Qing Dynasty once mentioned that
清朝末期の西洋人宣教師はかつてこう述べた。
Why are there so many front halls?
なぜ前堂がこんなにたくさんあるのでしょうか？
They also observed that more
彼らはまた、より多くのことを観察しました
Then what he said was
すると彼が言ったのは、
Because that's a funnel shaped bay
漏斗状の湾だから
That tide is so big
その潮はとても大きいです
So he becomes that whale's trap
それで彼はクジラの罠になる
Will suck this goldfish over and die here
この金魚は吸い込まれてここで死ぬだろう
So this is a more scientific statement
つまり、これはより科学的な記述です
But even if the current scientific research is not clear
しかし、たとえ現在の科学的研究が明確ではなかったとしても、
Why is there Jintun
なぜジントゥンがいるのか
Why did Jintun cut the money and go there
なぜジントゥンはお金を切り詰めてそこに行ったのか
In fact, there are many sayings now, and there is no specific one.
実際、今では多くのことわざがあり、特定のことわざはありません。
It is a conclusion that can fully explain
十分に説明できる結論です
Next we'll look at the scale
次にスケールを見ていきます
So we're going to look at the scale
それではスケールを見てみましょう
First, let's take a look at a record in Taiwan.
まずは台湾での記録を見てみましょう。
This record is in the ninth year of the dragon
この記録は辰九年のものです。
Nasutu, the civil governor, once reported that
那須都知事はかつて次のように報告した。
That last year was December 18 of the previous year
昨年は前年の12月18日でした
Baishatun in Hokuriku, Taiwan
台湾・北陸の白沙屯
Baishatun is in the area of ​​the current night
白沙屯は今日の夜あたりにあります
that all night with that
一晩中それと一緒に
22 very large fish
とても大きな魚が22匹
That mow dives into that sea
あの草はあの海に飛び込む
What about the head he said?
彼が言った頭はどうですか？
The mouth of the big tent fish is four feet wide
大きなテントフィッシュの口の幅は4フィートです
That belly is two tent tail big heptapod
そのお腹は2つのテントテールの大きなヘプタポッドです
Then his description said that the tail is very similar to the tail of a shrimp
すると彼の説明によると、その尻尾はエビの尻尾にとても似ているとのこと。
But it's fish body, etc. There are some related records
ただし、魚体などです。関連する記録がいくつかあります。
It's not dead yet, it's screaming like a cow, that cow is screaming
まだ死んではいない、牛のように叫んでいる、あの牛が叫んでいる
At that time, it was not yet fully
その時はまだ完全ではなかったのですが、
It's just that the tide may not have fully receded yet.
ただ、まだ完全に潮は引いていないのかもしれない。
It's the shallow tide
浅い潮です
don't know what it's called
何と呼ばれているかわかりません
more interesting it has a follow up
もっと興味深いのはフォローアップがあることです
It was when this mantra was reported to the former Dragon Emperor
この真言が先代龍帝に報告されたときのことである。
The former Dragon Emperor later issued an order
元龍帝は後に命令を出した
Just pointed down and said show me that fish painting
ただ下を指さして、その魚の絵を見せてと言った
Later, Nasu land was called Taiwan government.
その後、那須の地は台湾政府と呼ばれるようになりました。
After painting the soil
土を塗った後
Dust to the former Dragon Emperor
元竜帝へのダスト
But now we are on the Forbidden City archives
しかし今、私たちは紫禁城のアーカイブにいます
It's a pity I can't find this soil
この土が見つからないのが残念です
In addition, of course, the above is the record of the mantra
なお、上記はもちろんマントラの記録です
Below we are the records of Taiwan's government system
以下は台湾の政府システムの記録です。
That description isn't much different either.
その説明もあまり変わりません。
In addition, comrades were in Yilan in 1872
さらに、同志は1872年に宜蘭にいました。
This seaport in Gemaran
ゲマランのこの港
It is now the estuary of Lanyang Creek
現在は蘭陽溪の河口となっている。
There are 7 heavy rains also cut shallow in that place
あの場所も浅く切れて7回の大雨が降った
At the same time, if you intend to entrust it to Danshui, you will also cut shallow
同時に淡水に任せるつもりなら浅切りもします
that's pretty big
それはかなり大きいです
Then in 1881
そして1881年に
This deep storm also reported that in the Hengjiang area
この激しい嵐により、横江地域でも次のようなことが報告されました。
Where is this Hengjiang?
ここは横江どこですか？
It's probably a little bit inside the Qiantang River
おそらく銭塘江の少し内側だろう。
There are a lot of this fish dove dive
この魚のダイビングはたくさんあります
inexplicable
不可解
Its inexplicable name is very large
その不可解な名前は非常に大きいです
even that boat iron lock
あのボートの鉄錠さえも
It seems that the iron locks all the ones near the Hengjiang River
横江の近くのものはすべて鉄でロックされているようです
Stopped, the boat can't pass
止まっているのでボートは通れません
That record is the one I found with the largest number
そのレコードは私が見つけた最大の番号のものです
Qiantangjiang
銭塘江
This is the pigeon dive of a certain countryman
これは某田舎者の鳩飛び込みです
That this one is in a foreign country
これが外国にあるということ
are dead
死んでいます
The records of Jintun in Gequan in the traditional literature
伝統文献における葛泉の金屯の記録
Some records are very clear and some are very exaggerated
非常に明確な記録もあれば、非常に誇張された記録もあります
The number is somewhat, for example, a few examples
その数は、たとえば、いくつかの例です。
There is a record that once recorded that it was more than a hundred feet
かつては100フィート以上あったという記録が残っている
Of course we will think this is an exaggeration
もちろんこれは誇張だと思われるでしょう
Anyway, it's an adjective, so we have to take it seriously.
いずれにせよ、これは形容詞なので、真剣に受け止める必要があります。
However, there are some records that the recorded size is very fine
ただし、記録サイズが非常に細かいという記録もいくつかあります
Most of the records can be seen
ほとんどの記録が見られる
That is, if we look at the three grids in front
つまり、手前の 3 つのグリッドを見ると、
That is, the largest number is about six feet to ten feet.
つまり、最大数は約 6 フィートから 10 フィートです。
previous most
前回の
But there is a second one that is tens of feet long
しかし、長さ数十フィートの2番目のものがあります
This one is at the back where there are nineteen records
これは19枚のレコードがある後ろにあります
Probably we can see from this record
おそらくこの記録からも分かると思いますが、
It's the approximate number
おおよその数値です
Probably from this size to that size
おそらくこのサイズからあのサイズまで
Most of them are under 20 accounts
そのほとんどは 20 アカウント未満です
That's probably the place where the yellow color is on top of me now.
おそらく今、私の頭上にある黄色の場所です。
Said about 20 tents about 60 meters
約60メートルのテント約20張と言う
In fact, this is to use the official account to go to that
実は、これは公式アカウントを使用してそこにアクセスすることです
But what we need to know is that the Chinese folk
しかし、私たちが知っておく必要があるのは、中国人が
That is to say, every place they have will have their own one called Xiaozhang
つまり、それぞれがXiaozhangと呼ばれる独自のものを持つことになります。
That is, they are like our golden food in private
つまり、私たちの黄金の食べ物のようなものです
Gold grain is not the same
金の粒は一つとして同じではない
The public gold is different from the general Taiwan gold
パブリックゴールドは通常の台湾ゴールドとは異なります
that would be relatively small
それは比較的小さいでしょう
So that is to say, if we convert it into the relatively small folk tent
つまり、比較的小型の民族テントに換算すると
It may be relatively smaller
比較的小さいかもしれません
But we, I really can't find out what the number of its luxury tents is in each place, and I don't remember much.
しかし、私たちには、その豪華なテントが各地に何個あるのか、まったく調べられず、あまり覚えていません。
Probably strictly speaking, if we divide it by two-thirds or half
おそらく厳密には3分の2か半分で割ると、
The size of this is about four or five
大きさは4～5個くらいです
It's about 40 to 50 meters at most, and it's already very big.
せいぜい40～50メートルくらいで、もうかなり大きいです。
In fact, pigeons dive these big fish in the sea
実際、ハトはこれらの大きな魚を海に潜ります
It's what it's called. It's different in different places.
それは単にそう呼ばれているだけで、場所によって異なります。
all we've just said
私たちが今言ったことすべて
The picture we see below is also a picture of the West
下の写真も西洋の写真です
also a kind of engraving
彫刻の一種でもある
People's paintings are relatively normal
人の絵は比較的普通
And this pair is interesting
そしてこのペアも面白いですね
That is, he recorded the scene and still has the size of an elephant
つまり、彼はそのシーンを記録しましたが、まだ象ほどの大きさを持っています
Compared with the military instrument of the pigeon dive
ピジョンダイブの軍用具と比較
and horses and people
そして馬も人も
In fact, it is impossible to exaggerate to say more than 60 meters
実際、60メートル以上と言っても過言ではありません
That size is actually very, very scary
そのサイズは実際にはとてもとても怖いです
probably unlikely
おそらく可能性は低い
The following is an analysis of some cases of death
以下はいくつかの死亡例の分析です。
Some records will be recorded in a special way
一部のレコードは特別な方法で記録されます
that is why he died
それが彼が死んだ理由です
For example, there is a record that said he
たとえば、彼はこう言ったという記録がある。
There was a man whose father was an official in Haicheng County, Zhangzhou Prefecture
漳州県海城県の役人を父に持つ男がいた
One day when he was an officer, he saw two big fish peeling beans on the sea
彼が将校だったある日、海で二匹の大きな魚が豆の皮を剥いているのを見た。
Three days after the peeling, a fish got stuck on the reef in the sea
剥がしてから3日後、海のサンゴ礁に魚が引っかかってしまいました
Can't move on the reef next to the Han
ハンの隣のサンゴ礁では動けない
Probably one of them has already left
おそらくそのうちの一人はすでに出発したでしょう
Then this money cutting died on this reef
そしてこの金儲けはこのサンゴ礁で死んだ
We know that even the gold species will actually supplement their own kind.
私たちは、金種でさえ実際には同じ種を補うことを知っています。
For example, Fu Jin is the most familiar to everyone.
たとえば、誰にとっても最もよく知られているのは傅瑾です。
So he asked Fujin to attack those such as blue gold or virtual gold
そこで彼は風神にブルーゴールドやバーチャルゴールドなどを攻撃するよう依頼した。
Then this record may be relatively speaking
そうすると、この記録は比較的に言えるかもしれない
A record of Fu Jin going to attack other gold classes
苻進が他の金クラスを攻撃しに行った記録
This is Fukin
フキンです
Bite other coppers
他の銅を噛む
Also, it will be recorded that
また、次のように記録されます。
It is especially easy to cut money in the gold mine during the storm
嵐の間、金鉱山では特にお金が減りやすい
This was about seven or eight years ago
これは7、8年くらい前の話です
In this place in Haiyan County, Northern Subei
素北北部海塩県のこの場所
There is a photo of that township cutting money
その町が金を切り詰めている写真がある
many people run
多くの人が走っています
It is even recorded that
ということさえ記録されている
It is said that some people cut the meat and cooked it
肉を切って調理した人もいたと言われています。
Another record is that the tide suddenly rose
もう一つの記録は、潮が突然上がったことです
In particular, the typhoon washes up the sea water in the nearby sea area.
特に台風により、近海域では海水が打ち上げられます。
Traditionally, this kind of sea area will be called
伝統的にこの種の海域はこう呼ばれます。
would push some really big fish up the shore
本当に大きな魚を岸まで押し上げるだろう
After the push they cut the money
プッシュの後、彼らは資金を削減した
This record is relatively more
この記録は比較的多い
This is a photo from France
これはフランスからの写真です
After the storm, this virtual crystal was left in that place
嵐のあと、あの場所に残された仮想のクリスタル
What's more special is that there are two records related to the earthquake
さらに特別なのは、地震に関する記録が2件残っていることだ。
But those earthquakes are actually far behind in time.
しかし、それらの地震は実際には時間よりはるかに遅れています。
We're not entirely sure if it's just an earthquake under the sea.
それが単なる海底地震なのかどうかは完全にはわかりません。
Sometimes there are records of some heavy rain
時々大雨の記録もある
It dies and is slaughtered on the sea
死んで海で屠られる
This can be seen in the modern photos I collected
これは私が集めた現代の写真で見ることができます
The most frequently documented is why they cut money
最も頻繁に文書化されるのは、彼らが資金を削減する理由です
I mean, they go after fishing boats or merchant ships.
それは彼らが漁船や商船を狙うということだけです
Keep chasing and chasing, the boat will sail in
追いかけて追いかけ続ければボートは出航する
That river port, they still continued to chase
あの川の港、彼らはまだ追いかけ続けた
As a result, the river channel inside is relatively shallow.
そのため、内部の河道は比較的浅くなっています。
he cut shallow
彼は浅く切りました
There are many records of this kind in the Qing Dynasty
清朝にはこの種の記録がたくさんあります。
And this place in the south of the Yangtze River is very special
そして、長江の南にあるこの場所は非常に特別です
Like this place is the home of Xinfu in the north of Zhejiang, Pingwu County
この場所は浙江省北部、平武県の新府の本拠地のようです
scam this place
この場所を騙す
Finally we're going to do a tidy up
最後に整理整頓をしていきます
there is a cultural explanation for that cut
そのカットには文化的な説明がある
In fact, when the Chinese explain this about the fact that the military settlements are shallow
実際、中国人が軍事和解が浅いという事実についてこれを説明すると、
Sometimes it's you speaking from your current perspective
時にはあなたが現在の視点から話していることもあります
is relatively unlearnable
比較的学習不可能です
He used a kind of yin and yang or Mingxin.
彼は一種の陰と陽、あるいは明心（Mingxin）を使用しました。
For example, after the Song Dynasty, this military settlement began to appear.
たとえば、宋の時代以降、この軍事集落が現れ始めました。
It's actually the dragon king.
まさに竜王です。
Throw some of that misbehaving or guilty fish into the army
行儀の悪い魚や罪を犯した魚を軍隊に放り込んでください
where to rush to land
どこに急いで着陸するか
so he will be
だから彼はそうなるだろう
push inland
内陸に押し込む
This earliest record is the same as what was just mentioned
この最も古い記録は今述べたものと同じです
It started to appear in the heavy rain in Jiujiang before Li Hou's ancestral song
九江の大雨の中で、李侯の先祖の歌が流れる前に現れ始めました。
Of course, similar records are also mentioned in Ouyang Xiu's poems later.
もちろん、同様の記録は、後の欧陽秀の詩にも記載されています。
Until the Qing Dynasty, there was still the same saying
清の時代までは同じことわざがありました
That is to say, Jin Tun Geqian is because of his guilt
つまり、Jin Tun Geqianは罪悪感があるからです
before exile after guilty conviction
有罪判決を受けて追放される前
Kairyumaru or Kami will take his eyes off
海龍丸かカミが目を離すだろう
As a result, he lost his way
その結果、彼は道に迷ってしまった
This was also said in Taiwan at the end of the Qing Dynasty
清朝末期の台湾でも言われていました。
In addition, there is another special
さらに、もう一つ特別なことがあります
Sometimes before the song, it is because he is pressed by a big magic shrimp
時々、歌の前に大きな魔法のエビに押されるからです
Of course, this big shrimp is actually linked to what we just talked about.
もちろん、この大きなエビは、実は先ほどの話とつながっています。
The one that was confiscated by Kairyu Maru
海龍丸が没収したもの
Of course, this magical shrimp may actually be pressing the big fish to push it onto the land.
もちろん、この魔法のエビが実際に大きな魚を陸に押し上げようとしているのかもしれません。
So there will be some records like this
このような記録がいくつかあるでしょう
But sometimes if we interpret the common people like this
でも時々、私たちが一般の人々をこのように解釈すると、
Probably the result of his visual misreading
おそらく彼の視覚的な読み間違いの結果だろう
because of some big false alarms
いくつかの大きな誤報のせいで
Especially when he rolls on the sea
特に彼が海の上を転がるとき
when his two fins rolled over the sea
彼の2つのひれが海の上を転がったとき
It's like two big boils of shrimp
大きなエビが2尾茹でられたようなものです
So let's take a look, very much like
それでは見てみましょう、とても似ています
So if you look from far away on the coast
だから遠くの海岸から見てみると
I thought it was just a shrimp
ただのエビかと思ってた
At the same time, when he was active with him
同時に、彼と一緒に活動していたとき、
there will be other Jintun species next to it
その隣には他のJintun種があります
Maybe soon there will be Jintun class to cut the money
おそらくすぐにJintunクラスがあり、お金を削減するでしょう
They think this is the fish that God Shrimp was charged with
彼らはこれが神エビが告発された魚だと考えている
Interestingly, a saying that appeared later is called Runyu
興味深いことに、後に登場したことわざは「Runyu」と呼ばれています
I mean they observe I don't know if it's true
つまり、彼らは観察しているということですが、それが本当かどうかはわかりません
It means that generations began to observe that
それは、世代がそれを観察し始めたことを意味します
That Jintun Geqian at this time
この時の金屯格謙
often occurs during the lunar year
旧暦の年に起こることが多い
Especially the generation in the north of the Yangtze River estuary in northern Jiangsu
特に江蘇省北部の長江河口以北の世代
There are many records about this kind of legend.
この種の伝説に関する記録は数多くあります。
So it is the so-called run fish legend
いわゆるランフィッシュ伝説ですね
It will be there in the year of Meifeng Runnian
美峰潤年年にはそこにあるでしょう
That Jintun was pushed ashore
金屯が岸に押し上げられたこと
After the Qing Dynasty, it became more detailed
清朝以降はさらに詳しくなった
say that every year
毎年そう言う
The fish that is pushed on will be very compatible with the current year's effect
押し込まれた魚は今年の効果と相性抜群です
and looks alike
そして似ています
For example, if it is the year of the child, it looks like a mouse
例えば子年だとねずみっぽいです
In that ugly year, his head will be like a bull
その醜い年に、彼の頭は雄牛のようになるだろう
Well now we'll see later
さて、後で見てみましょう
Then this saying goes all the way to the Republic of China
そして、この格言は中華民国にまで伝わります。
In the early years, there was a famous fortune teller
昔、有名な占い師がいました。
This occultist is called Father Yuan
このオカルティストは袁神父と呼ばれています
He's still in that secret book of his
彼はまだその秘密の本の中にいます
also said that in 1909 when he
彼も1909年にこう言った。
He and his friends are in Dongtai County
彼と彼の友人たちは東台県にいます
Dongtai County is also the north bank of the Yangtze River
東台県は長江の北岸でもあります。
This place mentioned that there is such a phenomenon
この場所にはそのような現象があると記載されていました
Then he started to push according to that over there.
それから彼はそれに応じてそこに押し始めました。
Speak as if there is something wrong with Sa
Saに何か問題があるかのように話す
in fact it is
実際それは
Now we'll look ridiculous
今ではばかばかしいものに見えるでしょう
Sometimes it will be more detailed
場合によってはさらに詳しくなります
It was during the Runnian period
それはルンニアン時代のことでした
he these and that were pushed into the rain
彼はあれもこれも雨の中に押し込まれた
This typhoon is often accompanied by water
この台風は水を伴うことが多い
So this is understandable as we just said
したがって、これは先ほど述べたように理解できます
That's when the typhoon
そんな時に台風が
There will be a lot of that big rain appearing on the sea
あの大雨が海にたくさん降るでしょう
That's when I talked about the typhoon just now
さっき台風の話をしたときです
Later there will be that
後はそういうこともあるだろう
Of course, this is a result of two interconnected
もちろん、これは 2 つの相互接続の結果です。
Then let's take a look at this phase-by-line phase-by-line phase-by-line
それでは、このフェーズごとに見てみましょう。
This is near the mouth of the Yangtze River
ここは長江の河口近くです
It's the Legend of Runyu compared to that
それに比べたらルニュの伝説だよ
After the Qing Dynasty
清朝以降
Being demoted by the Sea Dragon King combined with the legend of Runyu
ルニュの伝説と合わせて海竜王に降格される
Of course it is more detailed
もちろんもっと詳しいですよ
Let's see what this one looks like now
これが今どのように見えるかを見てみましょう
If it works
うまくいけば
is it a bit like a snake
ちょっとヘビっぽいですか？
so they may be on the sea
だから彼らは海にいるかもしれない
Because of the angle, the head of the gold class is different
角度の関係でゴールドクラスのヘッドは異なります
so they start talking nonsense
それで彼らはナンセンスなことを話し始める
In short, the legend of running fish is a process of accumulation
つまり、魚を走らせる伝説は積み重ねの過程である
The last part we're going to talk about is
最後にお話しするのは、
This batch was ancient
このバッチは古いものでした
Because in ancient times, when talking about cutting money in Jintun
なぜなら、昔、金屯でお金を切るというと、
often use a word
よく言葉を使う
Just treat them as dragon sea dragons
ドラゴンシードラゴンとして扱ってください
or Dragon King Dragon
または龍王ドラゴン
So we're going to see after Dragon's Dive
ドラゴンズダイブのその後を見てみましょう
what's the end
終わりは何ですか
The first record is the only one I found
最初のレコードは私が見つけた唯一のレコードです
There is a record of release
リリース記録あり
This record has appeared in the Guang Department for three years
この記録は広省に3年間掲載されています
In the place of Heavy Army Island
重軍島の代わりに
There is a language about seven or eight feet long before the song
歌の前に7、8フィートほどの長さの言語があります
but it's a special place
でもここは特別な場所です
Seven or eight feet is actually not too big
7フィートか8フィートは実際には大きすぎません
But it found something on it
しかし、その上に何かを見つけました
this one has a silver medal
これは銀メダルを持っています
The silver medal reads "Kangxi Seven Years Released"
銀メダルには「康熙七年釈放」と書かれている
That is to say, the phrase
つまり、この言葉は、
In fact, in the seventh year of Kangxi
実は康熙7年に
once cut shallow after shallow cut
一度浅くカットした後、浅くカット
pushed it back to the surface
それを表面に押し戻しました
It's still on the fish well in the middle
まだ魚の真ん中にしっかり付いています
hanging a silver medal
銀メダルを吊るす
but i feel
でも私は感じます
How to hang the silver medal
銀メダルの掛け方
how is he hanging on the neck of this fish
彼はどうやってこの魚の首にぶら下がっているのですか
Will it fall? It's unlikely.
落ちますか? それはありそうにありません。
that this
これは
I think it might be a bit fictitious
ちょっと架空の話かも知れませんが、
But no matter that he mentioned this matter
しかし、彼が何を言ったとしても
That is to say, the Chinese used to be
つまり中国人はかつては
have put this
これを置きました
The goldfish rescued
救出された金魚
push him back to sea such a record
彼を海に押し戻すような記録
In fact, let's see some
実際にいくつか見てみましょう
Then we were going to talk about the record just now
それからさっきレコードについて話そうと思ってたんだけど
When Jintun was pushed back to sea, he had resisted Qi for seven years
金屯が海に押し戻されたとき、彼は7年間斉に抵抗していた
That connects to that later resisting Qi for seven years
それはその後の7年間のQiへの抵抗につながります
These 100 years
この100年
Is that so?
そうですか？
Jintun with such a long life
こんなに長生きのジントゥンさん
Actually there are
実際にはあります
It's the referendum
住民投票だよ
The referendum gold once recorded that he lived two hundred years
かつて国民投票の金貨には、彼が二百歳まで生きたと記録されていた
so but we don't know
だから、私たちには分かりません
Was that referendum money just now?
さっきの住民投票は金だったのか？
good
良い
In fact, what I just said is a lot of this
実際、私が今言ったことの多くはこれに当てはまります
The pigeon dog incident is often used to fall into the cage
ハト犬事件は檻に落ちるためによく使われる
that from the cage or something
それは檻か何かから
It's just that they don't know why this thing is here
ただ、なぜこれがここにあるのか彼らには分からないのです
So it is often said that they all thought they fell from the sky
それで彼らは皆空から落ちてきたと思ったとよく言われます
Therefore, many records mentioned above mean that
したがって、上記の多くの記録は次のことを意味します。
This cage fell from the sky
この檻は空から落ちてきた
after falling in that
それに陥った後
Then there are some records that say there are some officials
それから、何人かの役人がいたという記録がいくつかあります
That one even splashed water on him
その人は彼に水をかけさえしました
Tell the common people to keep pouring water on him
一般の人々に彼に水を注ぎ続けるように言いなさい
Because he may be in pain over there
彼はあそこで苦しんでいるかもしれないから
call over there
そこに電話する
because he's about to splash
彼は今にも飛び散るから
So ask the common people to pour water on him
そこで庶民に彼に水をかけるように頼みます
But splashing water is useless
でも水しぶきはダメだよ
Because later he only wanted him
だって後は彼だけが欲しかったから
If he does not return to the law, he must die
法に戻らないなら死ななければならない
died three days later
3日後に亡くなった
The meaning of Liao disaster really needs to be recorded
遼の災害の意味は本当に記録される必要がある
What about the local county magistrate?
地元の郡判事はどうですか？
I used this straw tin for 80 yuan
このストロー缶を80元で使いました
cover this dragon
このドラゴンをカバーします
In addition is
さらに、
Still worshiping him there
今でもそこで彼を崇拝している
then you can see that is to say
そうすれば、つまり、
It's impossible for a so-called dragon to fall from the sky
いわゆるドラゴンが空から降ってくることはあり得ない
He must have somehow been washed into the river
何らかの理由で川に流されたに違いない
or the one that fell on the beach
あるいは浜辺に落ちたもの
Then finally we're going to start talking about this sacrifice.
そして最後に、この犠牲について話し始めます。
It is the one with the most sacrifices
最も犠牲が多いのはそれだ
The most sacrificed child is that he was cut off
最も犠牲になった息子は切り捨てられたことだ
meat cut to death
切り殺された肉
This sacrificial boy is more cruel
この犠牲の少年はもっと残酷です
Those songs are very detailed
それらの曲は非常に詳細です
Then this sacrificial boy is a sacrificial ceremony in the early years of the Southern Song Dynasty
そして、この犠牲の少年は南宋初期の犠牲の儀式です
Sacrifice is also very meticulous
犠牲も非常に細心の注意を払っています
It also talks about cutting this off
これを切ることについても話します
How much does Jin's meat sell for?
ジンの肉はいくらで売れますか？
It sells for more than 200 yuan per catty
1斤あたり200元以上で売れる
It took 10 days to cut it
カットするのに10日かかりました
There are many related sacrifices, so we won't go into details
関連する多くの犠牲があるので、詳細には触れません
Here is an example
ここに例があります
Some people were poisoned to death after eating this golden meat
この黄金の肉を食べて毒殺された人もいた
maybe that one is corrupted
たぶんそれは壊れています
is that he is dead
彼は死んでいるということです
And corruption results in children eating
そして汚職によって子供たちは食事をすることになる
Then some are sick and some are dead
そして、ある者は病気になり、ある者は死亡する
We also have photos and we can see that Jintunei is dead.
写真もあり、ジントゥネイが亡くなっていることがわかります。
In fact, he has already started to rot, the skin is already there
実際、彼はすでに腐り始めており、皮膚はすでにそこにあります
And the most common one
そして最も一般的なのは
A lot of people cut it off and didn't eat it
切り取って食べなかった人も多い
mostly boiled oil
ほとんどが沸騰した油
The record of boiling oil has been around since a long time ago.
油を沸騰させるという記録は昔からあります。
There are many examples, so we won't go into details
例はたくさんあるので詳しくは説明しません
This is Japan, they do not have a business. There is a picture in it
ここは日本です、彼らにはビジネスがありません。そこには写真があります
After cutting the upper part of the body
胴体上部をカットした後
A picture of them starting to boil oil
油を沸騰させ始めている写真
sometimes there are some
時々いくつかあります
Their skeletons will leave some fundamental
彼らの骨格はいくつかの基本的なものを残します
just let us know
私たちに知らせてください
This is Jintun using the ones from Jintun as some building materials
これは金屯のものを建材として使用している金屯です。
The most commonly seen is Jintun's
最もよく見られるのはJintunのものです
Especially the bones that should be gold are used as bridges
特に金であるべき骨が橋として使われている
There are many records of this
このことに関する記録はたくさんあります
This is the photo of the golden fish bone of Lanji
これは蘭吉の金魚の骨の写真です
In addition, some people regard it as a good pillar
また、良い柱とみなす人もいます
The most special thing in Zhuang Liangzhu is that there is a photo
荘良渚の最も特別な点は、写真があることです。
Let's look at that photo first
まずはその写真を見てみましょう
There is a photo in the period of the Republic of China
中華民国時代の写真あり
It is mentioned that there is a magnetic hall in their family
彼らの家族には磁気ホールがあると言われています
There is a Wuliang in the middle of the magnetic hall
磁気ホールの真ん中に武梁があります
a string of words written on it
そこに書かれた一連の単語
That string of characters is this
その文字列はこれです
In the 20th year of Qianlong in the Qing Dynasty, the first day of the first lunar month
清の乾隆20年の旧暦正月1日
word entry
字入
It was the one that ran into Hong Kong with myself
一緒に香港に逃げ込んだやつだ
It is the oracle bone of a sea mound in Hong Kong Harbor
香港港の海塚の神託骨です
used oracle bones to make their Wuliang
武梁を作るために甲羅の骨を使用した
It also has the string of words written on it
そこにはまだ文字が書かれています
this is very special
これはとても特別なことです
In fact, there are many records of unscrupulous temples or homes.
実際、悪徳寺院や住宅の記録は数多くあります。
don't talk
話さないでください
There is also a record that Xiaojin was taken as a specimen after being separated from Qianqian.
小金は銭前から引き離された後、標本として採取されたという記録もある。
This has come after the Republic of China
これは中華民国の後に起こった
There is probably only one record that I found
おそらく私が見つけたレコードは 1 つだけです
But it is also possible that there are
しかし、ある可能性もあります
But it's not recorded
でも記録されてないよ
In addition, sometimes it will be displayed in some places
また、場所によっては表示されることもあります
For example, there are some temples that are most often released
たとえば、最も頻繁に解放される寺院がいくつかあります。
For example, Xu Yue’s Jianwen Road talks about the water temple in Laizhou, Shandong.
たとえば、Xu Yueの『Jianwen Road』では、山東省莱州市の水寺について語っています。
Saw some big fish skeletons in that place
その場所で大きな魚の骸骨を見た
In addition, he also said that he used to be in the area of ​​Haizhou Joint Venture Port
さらに、彼はかつて海州合弁港の地域にいたとも述べました
I saw that the common people used this fishbone to make old things, etc.
庶民がこの魚の骨を使って古いものなどを作っているのを見ました。
This is the vanity of gold
これが金の虚しさだ
It's the Xu on the mouth
口元の徐です。
it's funny
それはおかしいです
It's a photo of Xiyang
西陽の写真です
a photo of the west
西の写真
he can take it
彼はそれを受け入れることができる
that someone
あの誰か
The Chinese have ever taken him that
中国人は彼をこう受け取ったことがある
the one above
上のもの
This thing on the lake
湖の上にあるこれ
what to do
何をすべきか
take it to numbers
数字に落とし込む
This was recorded in the Tang Dynasty
これは唐の時代に記録されたものです
one more special
もう一つ特別な
It's in that Weihaiwei place
威海衛のあの場所にあります
placed at this gate of the park
公園のこのゲートに設置されています
that as a landscape
それは風景として
let's take a look
見てみましょう
That's the one
それだ
There is a place in Weihaiwei
威海衛に場所があります
The locals call it Shanjiao Park
地元の人々はそれを善交公園と呼んでいます
because it's hilltop
丘の上だから
this is gone now
これはもうなくなってしまった
Because I used to go to Weihaiwei
威海衛によく行ってたから
to see this place
この場所を見るために
this is gone
これはなくなった
that mouth this
あの口はこれ
where has been moved
どこに移動されたのか
This is the Republic of China
ここは中華民国です
More than ten years of the Republic of China
中華民国の十数年
we're coming to conclusions
私たちは結論に達しつつある
about the time
時間について
The conclusion is probably that
結論はおそらく次のとおりです
The vast majority of extant cases are
現存する事件の大部分は、
The main record is after the middle of the night in the Ming Dynasty
主な記録は明代の深夜以降
Before the middle of the night in the Ming Dynasty, it was relatively scattered
明代の深夜前は比較的分散していました
that last point
最後の点
Probably from the north bank of the Yangtze Estuary to that
おそらく長江河口の北岸からそこまで
Zhejiang Lane Shangan
浙江巷山安
that's the one
それだ
The coast of Zhoushan Islands
舟山諸島の海岸
It is the place where the most gold is mainly cut
主に金が最も多く切り出される場所です
Hangzhou Bay even has hundreds of
杭州湾には数百ものものもある
Records of Jintun Separation
金屯離散の記録
Generally speaking
一般的に言えば
Jintun's size
ジントゥンのサイズ
The size of the cutout is about 10 pieces in length
切り抜きのサイズは長さ10個くらいです
more than a few
いくつか以上の
There is a relatively high possibility that it may be virtual gold
仮想金の可能性は比較的高い
and most of what we can now determine
そして現在私たちが判断できることのほとんどは
some are smeared gold
一部は金が塗られています
gold class leave the world
ゴールドクラスがこの世を去る
It's this souvenir from our world
これは私たちの世界からのお土産です
Actually quite a lot
実はかなり多い
certainly
そうです
The most obvious is probably
最も明白なのはおそらく
The most common is Gouger
最も一般的なのはガウジャーです
So like I just said
だから今言ったように
It's going to be used as frozen food, bridge food.
冷凍食品、つなぎ食品として使用予定です。
Or chairs and stools and smart old
または椅子とスツールとスマートな古い
There are even dug into steel
鋼材にも掘り込まれたものもあります
Those who can raise whales have this
クジラを飼える人はこれを持っています
in traditional times
伝統的な時代に
because there's nothing like a museum or anything
博物館など何もないから
Oceanarium or something like that
海洋水族館とかそういうの
places to collect this skeleton about Jintun
金屯に関するこの骸骨を収集できる場所
So the most common way
したがって、最も一般的な方法は
is often placed in the square of the temple
寺院の広場によく置かれます
that's about binhai
それは浜海のことだ
Common people, they cut money from Jintun
庶民は金屯から金を切り取った
Explanations are of course full of cultural imagination
説明はもちろん文化的想像力に満ちています
Some of them are mystical
それらの中には神秘的なものもあります
I just said this
私はちょうどこれを言いました
That is to say, Dragonsea put this
つまり、ドラゴンシーはこれを置きました
The bad fish rushed into the army
悪い魚が軍隊に突入した
besides
そのほか
Later it was said about the so-called
後に、いわゆる
It will appear during the Lunar New Year, etc.
旧正月などに出現します。
later joined together
後に合流した
These actually represent a kind of thinking of human beings.
これらは実際に人間の思考の一種を表しています。
In fact, it has no scientific basis
実は科学的根拠はありません
The last thing I want to say is that
最後に言いたいのは、
After the great geographical discovery in the west
西部における偉大な地理的発見の後
Actually a lot of that kill goldfish
実際、その多くは金魚を殺します
Actually, and use this goldfish as a good fuel
実は、この金魚を良い燃料として使ってください。
and lubricant
そして潤滑剤
But in China relatively because
しかし、中国では比較的、
The frequency of goldfish cutting skirts is actually not too high
金魚がスカートを切る頻度は実はそれほど高くない
In addition, China except the South China Sea area
また、南シナ海地域を除く中国
There is a supplement to this custom
この習慣には補足があります
It's the Danmin of the South China Sea
南シナ海のダンミンです
It's a kind of ethnic minority of the sea
それは海の少数民族の一種です
they will kill jintun
彼らはジントゥンを殺すだろう
except them
彼らを除いて
Probably most of them will not take the initiative to go to sea without killing
おそらく彼らのほとんどは、人を殺さずに率先して海に行くことはないだろう。
In this process, there can actually be a result
このプロセスでは、実際に結果が得られる可能性があります
It's the kind of poisonous milk that we use in the sea.
それは海で使われているような有毒なミルクです。
is so relatively less
比較的少ないです
So some Western scholars say that this is a big difference
したがって、一部の西洋の学者は、これは大きな違いであると言っています
This is of course
これは当然です
Okay, I'll probably report it here, thank you all
わかりました、ここで報告します、皆さんありがとう
Don't pay attention to the artistic conception and then don't pay attention to the reality
芸術的な概念に注意を払わないでください、そして、現実にも注意を払わないでください
That's because of this, so it affects everyone and won't do it deliberately.
それはこのためであり、全員に影響を与えるものであり、意図的に行うものではありません。
detailed records
詳細な記録
The appearance of goldfish cutting money
お金を切る金魚の様子
then come again
それからまた来てください
japan for goldfish
金魚の日本
It seems that there are more records
他にも記録が残っているようです
Because it is Putin's tradition
それはプーチン大統領の伝統だから
Then it was mentioned at the end that
そして最後にこう言われました
Danming in southern China has such a culture
中国南部の丹明にはこんな文化がある
that's curious
それは興味深いです
Is the lightness of southern China the same as that of Japan?
中国南部の軽さは日本と同じでしょうか？
Is there any record of communication
通信記録はありますか
or mutual cultural influence
または相互の文化的影響
This related history
この関連の歴史
and then the third is
そして3番目は
It is recorded that there are
あることが記録されている
It is mentioned that PVT just now
今PVTについて言及されました
one word is
一言は
Everyone thinks it's weird because everyone thinks it's a weird thing
誰もがそれを奇妙だと思うから、誰もがそれを奇妙だと思う
Then or someone feels that it is
そうすると、あるいは誰かがそう感じます
It's the goldfish who's coming to worship
参拝に来たのは金魚です
Come to Dragon King, I have to swim back again
竜王のところへ来い、また泳いで戻らなければならない
then or something even a fallen dragon
それから落ちたドラゴンでも
dragon that fell from the sky
空から落ちてきたドラゴン
Then I'm curious, so the record inside
じゃあ気になるからその中のレコードを
mostly positive context
ほとんどポジティブな文脈
Still more negative context
さらにネガティブな文脈
Can positive or negative this be used as a
それはポジティブにもネガティブにもなり得るのでしょうか？
Will the current government use it to explain
現政府はそれを説明に使うだろうか
Oh because of the country we govern now
ああ、私たちが今統治している国のせいで
very common
ごく普通
That's why God has images to make auspicious omens
だからこそ、神は縁起の良い前兆をもたらす画像を持っているのです
It's more like a negative
むしろマイナスっぽいな
It is because the emperor of the previous era was married
前の時代の天皇が結婚していたからです
So this happened in the previous era
前の時代にもこんなことがあったんだね
This kind of imaginative thing
こういう想像力豊かなもの
Is it more positive or more negative?
それはよりポジティブですか、それともよりネガティブですか？
Can it have a
それはありますか？
An explanation of the social atmosphere of that era
当時の社会情勢を解説
Li Chang
リー・チャン
Okay, that's the first question.
さて、それが最初の質問です。
I think your question should be certain.
あなたの質問は確かであるべきだと思います。
probably because
おそらくだから
But we can't actually find real evidence
しかし、実際には本当の証拠は見つかりません
Because the Chinese, of course, basically
なぜなら中国人は基本的には、
He is a literati, he is more interested in art
彼は文人で、芸術にもっと興味があります
It's more about artistic conception, that's right.
芸術的な概念にもっと注意を払うのは間違いではありません。
But we might just have a possibility
でも、私たちには可能性があるかもしれない
Why does this kind of image data remain less
なぜこのような画像データが少なくなっているのか
The first is when this happened
1つ目は、これが起こったときのことです
possibly local
おそらく地元の
It is possible to find that gold and pigeons are both
金とハトは両方とも同じであることがわかります。
fishermen living by the sea
海辺に住む漁師たち
some local people
何人かの地元の人
Ordinary people, they may not actually have the ability to do this
普通の人には実際にはそんな能力はないかもしれない
Said to keep it and draw it
それを保管して描くと言われました
There are also some possibilities
いくつかの可能性もあります
It's a fetish. You can't draw a fetish.
それはフェチです、フェチを描くことはできません。
There is a tradition, for example,
例えば次のような伝統があります。
I've been to that years ago
何年も前に行ったことがある
Even three years ago, I went to the mainland for inspection.
３年前にも本土に視察に行きました。
I took a camera to take pictures of that god
その神様の写真を撮ろうとカメラを持ってきました
The person who took the tour was Zi Zi who didn’t let me take pictures
ツアーに参加してくれたのはZi Ziさんでしたが、写真は撮らせてくれませんでした。
I just said we don't have this opportunity in Taiwan
台湾ではこのような機会はないと言いました
He said we can't do it in this place
彼は、この場所ではそれはできないと言った
That is to say, the local people have been
つまり、地元の人たちは、
Even after the Cultural Revolution
文化大革命後も
But they are concerned about God
しかし彼らは神のことを心配しています
you can't take pictures of him
彼の写真を撮ることはできません
can't even draw
絵も描けない
This may also be to some extent
これもある程度はそうなるかもしれない
It can be explained that like the dragon
ドラゴンのようなものだと説明できます
Or fetish they may feel they shouldn't draw it
またはフェチの人はそれを描くべきではないと感じるかもしれません
This is my conjecture with no evidence
これは私の推測です、証拠はありません
The second question is whether this Danming has exchanged experience with Japan in their supplementary funds experience
2番目の質問は、このダンミン氏が日本との補完基金の経験を交換したことがあるかどうかです。
In fact, I can't see it at all from the literature.
実際、文献からは全く分かりません。
That is to say, this may also be the lack of literature
つまりこれも文献不足なのかもしれない
In fact, some people say that Danming, a sea group, appeared after the Southern Song Dynasty.
実際、海族の丹明は南宋以降に出現したという説もある。
Of course it was possible earlier
もちろん以前から可能でした
There is a group of people who may have traveled from Fujian to the Gulf of Tonkin in Vietnam.
福建省からベトナムのトンキン湾へ旅行したと思われる人々のグループがいます。
They are the group of people who live on the water, they don't go on land very much
彼らは水上で生活する人々のグループであり、陸上にはあまり行かない
That group of people occasionally
たまにあの人たちのグループが
but in some cases
しかし場合によっては
They go back to make up the money
彼らはお金を補うために戻ってきます
They don't dare to make up big money
彼らは大金を巻き上げる勇気はない
They found that tissue shoveled out in some seasons
彼らは、季節によっては組織がかき出されていることを発見しました
They shoot him with that fish mark
彼らはその魚のマークが付いた彼を撃ちます
After shooting him and letting him die at sea
彼を撃ち、海で死なせた後
slow down
徐行
drag it to the sand drag it to the sand to untie it
砂までドラッグしてください 砂までドラッグしてほどいてください
boil after disintegration
崩壊後に煮る
Because after all they need fuel at sea too
だって海上でも燃料が必要だから
so they are probably
だから彼らはおそらくそうだろう
but not too many
でも多すぎない
Records began to appear in the Ming Dynasty
明代に記録が出始めた
There was a Chongzhou in the Ming Dynasty
明代有一個重州
Fuzhi, a state of political virtue, began to record that
政治的美徳を備えた府治は、次のことを記録し始めた。
But tomorrow will make up money
でも明日はお金が戻ってくるよ
Every year, they will replenish paper towels in some seasons
毎年、季節によってはペーパータオルを補充します
Because we don't know how the group got here
グループがどのようにしてここに来たのかわからないからです
maybe he's ugly
もしかしたら彼は醜いのかもしれない
It was related to Japan very early on.
かなり早い段階から日本と関わりがありました。
Or stay in Japan for a long time and they are related
あるいは日本に長期滞在していれば関係がある
But there is absolutely no relevant research
しかし、関連する研究はまったくありません
Talking about the relationship between the two ethnic groups
二つの民族の関係について語る
Is there an absolute connection?
絶対的な関係はあるのでしょうか？
Even with current affairs that probably lack documentation
おそらく資料が不足しているであろう時事問題であっても
Of course everyone in Japan knows
もちろん日本国民なら誰でも知っています
Even now there are still people
今でも人がいる
Occasionally go to make up money
時々お金を補いに行く
So there's a documentary about a bay
湾についてのドキュメンタリーがあります
Inside a village bay
村の湾内
After they put him right into that bay
彼らが彼をその湾に放り込んだ後、
intercept it at that estuary
あの河口でそれを迎え撃つ
Then the whole sea is red
そうしたら海全体が赤くなる
cruel
残酷
what is the third question
3番目の質問は何ですか
I just want to know the positive side of the record.
私はただこの記録のポジティブな面を知りたいだけなのです。
think of me
わたしのことを考えて
In fact, I just mentioned the first earliest record
実際、先ほど最初の最古の記録について触れました。
It is the record of the Han Dynasty
漢の時代の記録です
He is recorded in five elements
彼は五つの要素で記録されています
It is recorded in it that when those phenomena appeared
そこには、それらの現象がいつ現れたかが記録されています
It's negative, it's the heavenly scene
それはネガティブです、それは天国の光景です
It's the emperor, you didn't do well
皇帝だよ、下手だったね
you can't handle some things
あなたはいくつかのことに対処できない
So that day has imagery
その日のイメージがあるので
This fetish was rushed up
このフェチは急遽登場しました
This is asking the emperor to recruit himself
これは皇帝に自らを徴兵するよう求めている
There are also adjustments to be made in terms of governance
ガバナンス面でも調整が必要
Later, it was extensively documented
その後、広範囲に文書化されました
on the local word
地元の言葉で
It is also often recorded in the will
遺言書にも記載されることが多い
in the will of course
もちろん意志の中で
You start with the words that will
あなたはそうなる言葉から始めます
I know it's a kind of care
それが一種の気遣いだとわかっている
It thinks that the appearance of this thing is not a good thing
この物の出現は良くないと思います
In addition, there are some literatures that say
また、次のように述べている文献もあります。
I didn't just talk about
ただ話したわけではない
that is to say some talk is to say
つまり、ある話はこう言うことです
as long as this kind of thing appears
こういうのが出てくる限りは
That reporter has a strong wind
あの記者は風が強い
Then we know that the southeast also sea
そうすれば、南東にも海があることが分かります
Especially in Zhejiang and Fujian
特に浙江省と福建省では
The most common occurrence is
最も一般的な現象は次のとおりです
What is the so-called big front behind the so-called big front
いわゆる大きな前線の背後にあるいわゆる大きな前線とは何ですか
It's a typhoon or a big cyclone
台風か大型低気圧ですね
Although not to the typhoon level
台風レベルではないものの、
But it will make the whole coast
でも海岸全体がそうなるだろう
Great changes in the weather began
天気の大きな変化が始まりました
So I saw an actual record in Zhejiang
そこで浙江省で実録を見てきました
They said that as long as they saw the sea station
海の駅さえ見ていればと彼らは言った
is Haiti
ハイチです
when it rolls and bounces like this on the sea
海の上でこうやって転がったり跳ねたりすると
Everyone should be careful and start to be on guard
みんなも気を付けて警戒を始めましょう
So in other words, fishermen off the coast
つまり沖合の漁師ということですね
in the eyes of ordinary people
普通の人の目には
If something like this happens, I'm afraid it will bring disaster.
このようなことが起こったら、災害が起こるのではないかと心配です。
There aren't too many positive records.
肯定的な記録はあまり多くありません。
It is usually considered strange that this appears
通常、これが表示されるのは奇妙だと考えられています
In fact, it includes one of the teasing disasters
実際、それにはからかい災害の 1 つが含まれています。
send it to this kind of thing, it will
このようなものに送信すると、
just show that it's not
そうではないことを示すだけです
That is to say, in ancient times
つまり古代では
The rating is not particularly high
評価は特に高くない
Because if something like this happens
だってこんな事が起きたら
Chinese people are actually curious
中国人は実は好奇心が強い
Most will take it down
ほとんどがそれを取り下げるだろう
but miscellaneous
でも雑多
Of course, that is why after the Ming Dynasty there were more
もちろん、それが明の時代以降さらに多くのことが起こった理由です。
It is because there are more written materials left than before
以前よりも多くの文書が残っているためです
So there are relatively many records
比較的記録が多いので
It may have been recorded before
以前に収録されていた可能性があります
But after a while some books were passed on privately
しかししばらくして、いくつかの本は個人的に渡されました
Or there are some official files
または公式ファイルがいくつかあります
Maybe he also reported to be an official
たぶん彼も役人であると報告した
but did not stay
しかし留まらなかった
So generally speaking
一般的に言えば
not too much positive
正面的不太多
usually taken as an image
通常はイメージ
not a good sign
良い兆候ではありません
right
右
Then we thank the teacher for bringing us today
それから、今日私たちを連れてきてくれた先生に感謝します
our wonderful speeches
私たちの素晴らしいスピーチ
Thanks
ありがとう
Okay, thank you
大丈夫ありがとう